(Raj:)You're wrong.
No, I'm not.
(Raj:)Yes, you are.
(Howard:)Settle this. Those
little animated pictures
(Howard:)on the Internet, are they
called "gifs" or "jifs"?
(Leonard:)Well, the G stands
for "graphics."
(Leonard:)That's a hard G,
so I'd say "gif."
W... The guy who invented
it says it's "jif."
(Howard:)I'm sorry, do you mean
the guy or the juy?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'll give you
three guesses
(Sheldon:)why I'm so irritated.
(Howard:)Something happened different
from the way you wanted it.
(Sheldon:)I guess news travels fast.
(Sheldon:)It's true,
a select group of scientists
(Sheldon:)was invited
to a weekend symposium
(Sheldon:)at a former home
of Richard Feynman,
(Sheldon:)and I wasn't included.
(Leonard:)Oh, Sheldon, I'm sure it's
not because they don't think
(Leonard:)you're an elite
scientist.
Yeah,
(Howard:)I bet you anything it's
just 'cause you're
a pain in the ass.
(Sheldon:)You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
(Leonard:)Look, you can spend
the rest of the day
(Leonard:)being bitter about this.
Agreed.
I was gonna say "or,"
but why bother?